Guide to the Vassar College Facilities Operations Records, 1800s-2021 (bulk 1908-1999)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series I. Administrative Files, 1879-2011
  - Vassar College Computer Rises All Correspondence, 1983 (Box 55)
  - [Student Housing] [Vassar Dormitory Rehabilitation Study], 1972 (Box 55)
  - [Faculty Housing] Faculty Housing Carl Koch and Assoc. Architects, 1965-1966 (Box 55)
  - [Faculty Housing] Spicer House, 1975 (Box 55)
  - [Faculty Housing] Parrish House (All Correspondence), 1967 (Box 55)
  - [Faculty Housing] Owner Correspondence, 1959-1966 (Box 55)
  - [Faculty Housing] Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958-1965 (Box 55)
  - [Faculty Housing] Clarke and Rapuano, 1960-1963 (Box 55)
  - [Alumnae House] Vassar College Alumnae House, 1982 (Box 55)
  - Vassar College Antennas, 1985 (Box 55)
  - [Avery Hall] Vassar College Avery, 1989 (Box 55)
  - [Athletics Facilities] Vassar College Athletic Field, 1973-1974 (Box 55)
  - Vassar College Facilities Offices, 1988 (Box 55)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Vassar College Blodgett, 1989 (Box 55)
  - [Baldwin Hall] Vassar College Baldwin, 1980 (Box 55)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Vassar College Computer Center, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Vassar College Exterior Railings, 1978 (Box 55)
  - [Cushing House] Vassar College Cushing, 1989 (Box 55)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Vassar College Animal Facilities Blodgett, 1990 (Box 55)
  - [Chapel] Vassar College Chapel, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Vassar College Facilities Rehab, 1990 (Box 55)
  - Ferry House, 1987 (Box 55)
  - Vassar College Head House at Skinner GRNHSE, 1984 (Box 55)
  - [ALANA Center] Vassar College ICC 6 College Activities, 1989 (Box 55)
  - [Jewett House] Vassar College Jewett, 1979 (Box 55)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Vassar College Kenyon Gym, 1986 (Box 55)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Vassar College Kenyon Entrance, 1979 (Box 55)
  - [Chicago Hall] Vassar College Phase II Language Lab, 1987 (Box 55)
  - [Town Houses] Laundry At Town Houses, 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Lockwood and Thompson Vassar College, 1979 (Box 55)
  - Vassar College Ramps Chicago Hall Computer Center Lockwood Library, 1980 (Box 55)
  - Vassar College Mabs, 1980 (Box 55)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College Ramp For Main Building, undated (Box 55)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Vassar College Mudd Chemistry, 1988 -1989; (2 folders) (Box 55)
  - [New England Building] Vassar College New England, 1990 (Box 55)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Vassar College Olmsted, 1981 (Box 55)
  - Vassar College President’s House, 1986 (Box 55)
  - [Powerhouse Theater] Vassar College Powerhouse Theater, 1990 (Box 55)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders, 1977-1978 (Box 55)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders 200 Drawings, 1988 (Box 55)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Furnishings, 1989 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Classroom 200 Drawings, 1988 (Box 56)
  - [Skinner Hall] Skinner Parking, 1972 (Box 56)
  - Vassar College Torch and Owl designs, 1985 (Box 56)
  - Vassar College Sun Dial, undated (Box 56)
  - [Swift Hall] Vassar College Swift and Metcalf, 1987 (Box 56)
  - Vassar College Misc Toilets, 1986, 1990 (Box 56)
  - [Town Houses] Vassar College Town Houses, 1975, 1986 (Box 56)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College Main Miscellaneous, 1969-1985 (Box 56)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College Main Hall Owner Correspondence, 1959-1963 (Box 56)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College Main Hall Miscellaneous, 1960, 1962 (Box 56)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College Main Hall Campbell Building Co., General Contractor, 1959 (Box 56)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College 2nd Floor Main, 1985-1986 (Box 56)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College First Floor Main, 1985, 1987 (Box 56)
  - Vassar College Juice Bar Proposal, 1986 (Box 56)
  - [Rockefeller Hall] Vassar College Rockefeller Hall, 1979-1980; (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - [Skinner Hall] Skinner Hall, 1980 (Box 56)
  - [Taylor Hall] Vassar College Taylor, 1979 (Box 56)
  - [Vassar College Farm] Vassar College Vassar Farm Bridge, 1990 (Box 56)
  - [New England Building] Vassar College New England BSMT Spec., 1990 (Box 56)
  - [Alumnae House] Vassar College Alumnae Ramp Specifications, 1990 (Box 56)
  - [Alumnae House] Vassar College Alumnae House Rump All Correspondence, 1990 (Box 56)
  - [New England Building] Vassar New England Manfredi Documents, 1990 (Box 56)
  - [New England Building] Vassar New England Job and Conference Reports, 1990 (Box 56)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Vassar College Blodgett Animal Facility, 1990 (Box 56)
  - [Wimpfheimer Nursery School] Vassar College Wimpfheimer Nursery School, 1986-1991 (Box 56)
  - [Powerhouse Theater] Vassar College Powerhouse Theater, 1990 (Box 56)
  - Vassar College Misc. Correspondence, 1962-1990; (3 folders) (Box 56)
  - [New England Building] Vassar New England All Correspondence, 1990 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Owners Correspondence, 1990 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Idema Documents, 1988 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Vassar College Contractor’s Correspondence, 1988-1990; (2 folders) (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Classroom Job Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Bidders, 1987 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Addendum, 1987 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Conference Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Office Rehabs. Bidders Correspondence, 1987 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Addendum No 1, 1987 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Furnishings, 1988 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Preliminary Design Report, 1987 (Box 56)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Edwards and Zuck, 1987-1989 (Box 56)
  - [Alumnae House] Vassar College Alt/Ren. Alumnae House All Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 56)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College Main Hall Goldstone and Dearborn, Architects, 1959-1960; (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College Main Hall - Conference Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 57)
  - [Main Building] Vassar College Main Hall Clarke and Rapuano Landscape Arch., 1959-1967 (Box 57)
  - [Chapel] Wooster School - Chapel and Honor Room Specifications, 1962 (Box 57)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Mudd Mechanical Repair [Bills], 1988-1989 (Box 57)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Classroom [Bills and Invoices], 1989 (Box 57)
  - Asbestos Abatement, 1984 (Box 57)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] [Mudd Mechanical Upgrade- Work Requests and Invoices], 1989 (Box 57)
  - [Raymond House] Raymond House Electrical Upgrade - Work Requests, Invoices and Specifications, 1989 (Box 57)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] [ACDC Waste Pumping System Orders], 1987-1988 (Box 57)
  - [Utilities] Alarm and Security System Payments, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
  - Lathrop House Fire Alarm and Electrical System Upgrade [Work Requests and Invoices], 1987-1989 (Box 57)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Electrical Distribution System Upgrade - Work Requests and Invoices, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
  - College and Raymond Ave. Asbestos Abatement, 1987 (Box 57)
  - [College Center - The Retreat] Retreat, 1988-1989 (Box 57)
  - Signage, 1986-1990 (Box 57)
  - Interior Signage, 1987 (Box 57)
  - Campus - Signage, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
  - [Raymond House] Rewire Raymond Hall, 1989-1990; (2 folders) (Box 57)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Mudd Upgrade Mechanical, 1987-1990 (Box 57)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Mudd Chemistry Building Punchlist, 1989-1990 (Box 57)
  - [Raymond House] Raymond Bathroom Upgrade, undated (Box 57)
  - Asbestos Management, 1989 (Box 57)
  - Asbestos Abatement, Letters Of Notification, 1989 (Box 57)
  - [Avery Hall] Avery Upgrade Offices, undated (Box 57)
  - [Rockefeller Hall] Technical Specifications - Rockefeller Hall Roof Repair and Installation Contract, 1989 (Box 57)
  - [Town Houses] Town House Boiler Replacement, 1989 (Box 57)
  - [Faculty Housing] Rombout House (Flagler House), Porch Pillar Replacement, 1989 (Box 57)
  - [Avery Hall] Avery Hall Roof Replacement, 1989 (Box 57)
  - [Kenyon Hall] Kenyon Roof Replacement, 1989 (Box 57)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Central Heating Plant Boiler Replacement, 1988-1990 (Box 57)
  - [Central Heating Plant] Boiler Room Repairs, Invoices, Time Sheets and Work Orders, 1989-1990 (Box 58)
  - [Williams House] Williams Plumbing Replacement, 1990 (Box 58)
  - [Student Housing] Terrace Apartments Heating Upgrade, 1989 (Box 58)
  - [Main Building] Main Rezone Housefellows [Work Orders], 1989 (Box 58)
  - [Davison House] Davison Energy Management, 1989 (Box 58)
  - [Raymond House] Raymond Hall Energy Management, 1989 (Box 58)
  - North Gate Parking Lot, 1989 (Box 58)
  - North Lot Rebuilding [Correspondence, Specifications and Permits], 1989 (Box 58)
  - [Blodgett Hall] Blodgett Wiring Upgrade, 1989 (Box 58)
  - [Rockefeller Hall] Rockefeller Wiring Upgrade, 1989 (Box 58)
  - [Raymond House] Rekey Raymond [Work Orders], 1989 (Box 58)
  - [Utilities] Campus Emergency Lighting [Work Orders], 1989 (Box 58)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] ACDC Upgrade Foyer [Work Orders, Invoices, Drawings and Plans], 1989-1989 (Box 58)
  - Loeb Art Center Record Change Orders, 1992-1993; (2 folders) (Box 58)
  - [Alumnae House] Vassar Alumnae House - Specifications and Plans, 1979-1990 (Box 58)
  - [New England Building] Specifications and Plans - New England Building, 1990 (Box 58)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Classroom Building - Folded Plans for Millwork, Ceiling, and Stairs, 1988; (4 folders) (Box 58)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Second Floor [Project Submittal and Plans], 1988; (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - [Chicago Hall] Chicago Hall - Vassar Language Lab [Proposal and Plans], 1988 (Box 59)
  - Head House at Skinner Greenhouse - Vassar College, Plans and Manuals, 1984 (Box 59)
  - [Rockefeller Hall] Vassar - Miscellaneous Plans, 1979-1980 (Box 59)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Lockwood Library [Plans for Ramp Railing], 1984 (Box 59)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Computer Center - Hollow Metal [Submittal Forms], 1984 (Box 59)
  - [Alumnae House] Alumnae Association of Vassar College Addition [Alumnae House Renovations], 1979 (Box 59)
  - Vassar Railings - Specifications and Plans, 1978-1980 (Box 59)
  - [Main Building] [Ramp Specifications], undated (Box 59)
  - [Skinner Hall] Head House Specifications, 1983 (Box 59)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Computer Center - Specifications for Alterations, 1984 (Box 59)
  - [Chicago Hall] Chicago Hall - Specifications for Alterations to the Language Laboratory, 1985, 1987; (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - [New England Building] Specifications for Alterations to Basement Floor, 1990 (Box 59)
  - [Main Building] Specifications for Office Rehabilitations and Second Floor, 1986 (Box 59)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry Building - Specifications for Elevator Installation, General Construction and Mechanical Work, 1977, 1987; (3 folders) (Box 59)
  - [Rockefeller Hall] Specifications for Alterations, 1979 (Box 59)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Lockwood Library - Specifications for Ramp, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Alterations for Main Building, Avery, Blodgett and Skinner Halls, 1980 (Box 59)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Classroom Building - Finished Hardware [Correspondence and Schedule], 1988 (Box 59)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Classroom Building - Plumbing, HVAC and Sprinkler Shop Drawings, 1989 (Box 59)
  - [Sanders Classroom] [Plumbing, HVAC and Sprinkler], Shop Drawings, 1988; (2 folders) (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Arch Shop Drawings, 1988 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Electrical Shop Drawings, 1988 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders, 1987-1988 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Historic Preservation, 1988 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Building - Contract and Job Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders ’88 - Punch Lists Classroom, 1989 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders - Furnishings and Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Classroom Move, 1989 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Construction Costs, 1987-1989 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Architectural Fees, 1987-1988 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Preliminary Expenditures, 1987 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders C.O. and Inspection and Guarantees, 1988-1989 (Box 60)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders - HVAC and Roofing, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders - Change Estimates, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - [Alumnae House] Alumnae House Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
  - [Avery Hall] Avery Hall Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
  - [College Center] College Center Energy Audit, undated (Box 61)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Computer Center Energy Audit, undated (Box 61)
  - [Davison House] Davison House Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
  - Lathrop House Energy Audit, undated (Box 61)
  - [Main Building] Main Building Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
  - [New England Building] New England ECM [Energy Audit], 1980-1981 (Box 61)
  - [Raymond House] Raymond House Energy Audit, 1983 (Box 61)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
  - [Sanders Physics] Sanders Physics Energy Audit, 1980 (Box 61)
  - Strong House Energy Audit, undated (Box 61)
  - Non Collusion Affidavit, undated (Box 61)
  - Tax Exemption Clause to Accompany Purchase Orders, undated (Box 61)
  - Freshman Parent’s Weekend, 1987 (Box 61)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] Heating - Rentals, 1986 (Box 61)
  - Price Changes - Hess, 1987 (Box 61)
  - IBM - Poughkeepsie Management Institute Conferences, 1987 (Box 61)
  - ID System, 1989 (Box 61)
  - Infra-Red Surveys, 1986 (Box 61)
  - Loss Prevention Surveys - IRI, 1986 (Box 61)
  - Oil Inventories, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Paging Systems, 1986 (Box 61)
  - Pest Control, 1985-1987 (Box 61)
  - Power Department, 1983-1988 (Box 61)
  - Project Lists, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Carriage Hill Property - Adjoining V.C. on Route 376, 1967-1987 (Box 61)
  - Property Tax Exemptions, 1987 (Box 61)
  - Property Tax Exemptions, 1986 (Box 61)
  - Collegeview Avenue Fence Line, 1970-1980 (Box 61)
  - Property - General, 1954-1988 (Box 61)
  - Property - Available for Lease or Purchase by Vassar College, 1965-1982 (Box 61)
  - Refrigeration Equipment - Contract, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Reunion, 1987 (Box 61)
  - Facilities Operations Staff Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - [Utilities] Design of Storm Sewer System, 1986 (Box 61)
  - Summer Programs, 1988 (Box 61)
  - Summer Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 61)
  - Summer Projects, 1986 (Box 61)
  - Summer Programs, 1986-1988 (Box 61)
  - [Utilities - Heating and Cooling] THERM, 1986 (Box 61)
  - [Utilities] Trash Collection - 1986-1988 (Box 61)
  - Tricentennial Celebration, 1987 (Box 61)
  - Uniforms, 1987 (Box 61)
  - United Way - 1985, 1986-1988 (Box 61)
  - Road Repairs, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - United Way (1989) (Box 61)
  - Vassar Lake, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Vendors, 1985-1987 (Box 61)
  - Wetlands, 1987 (Box 61)
  - [Utilities] Winter Break Curtailment 88/89 (operational, e.g. building temperatures), 1988 (Box 61)
  - [Utilities] Winter Weekend 88/89, 1988 (Box 61)
  - [Utilities] Winter Weekend - 1988 (Box 61)
  - [Utilities] Winter Break Curtailment - 1987, 1986-1987 (Box 61)
  - Loeb Art Center Project Manual Vol. I, 1991 (Box 62)
  - Loeb Art Center Project Manual Vol. II, 1991 (Box 62)
  - Loeb Art Center Project Manual Vol. III, 1991 (Box 62)
  - [College Center] College Center Addendums, 1973-1977 (Box 62)
  - [Library - Thompson] Library Progress Photographs, 1961-1972 (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] [Electrical Drawings HVAC], undated (Box 62)
  - [Library - Lockwood] [Electrical Drawings], 1976 (Box 62)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Vassar College Electrical Interconnection Diagrams Ansul Job No. 7255, 1975-1976 (Box 62)
  - [Library - Lockwood] [Vassar Library Sprinkler System], 1975 (Box 62)
  - [Library - Lockwood] [Vassar College Library Circuit Breaker Instruction Manual], 1976 (Box 62)
  - [Library - Lockwood] Library Addition - The Design Decision Making Process by Judith E. Schwartz, 1976 (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Mudd - Punch Lists, 1987-1990 (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Mudd Chemistry, 1985-1986 (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Project Expenditures, 1987 (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Mudd Air Conditioner, 1988 (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Mudd Building - Flack and Kurtz, 1987-1988 (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Mudd - Addendums 1, 2, 3, 1982 (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry Building, 1982 May - 1983 Dec (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry Building, 1981 Jan - 1982 Apr (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry Building Study, 1980 Dec (Box 62)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Mudd - Concrete and Soil Testing, 1982-1983 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Mudd Chemistry- Compressed Air Services, 1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Blinds and Shades, 1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Blueprint Transmittals, 1982-1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Door Alarm System, 1984-1985 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Electric - Underground Street Light Wiring, undated (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Electric, 1984-1986 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Energy Management System, 1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Mudd - Emergency Generator and Electric, undated (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Elevator, 1985 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Equipment Schedule - Mudd Chemistry Building, undated (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Fire and Temperature Alarm System, 1984-1985 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry - Finish Hardware, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Floor Plans, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Equipment and Furnishings, 1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. HVAC and Plumbing, 1983-1985 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] HVAC Building Services, Alarm System, 1985 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Punch Lists and Construction Reports, 1984-1988 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] HVAC - Mudd - Valve Charts, undated (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] HVAC Temperature Controls, 1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Renewal Parts Proposal, 1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Equipment Specifications, 1982 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Landscaping, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Chemistry - Metal Panel Color Selection, 1983 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Meters, undated (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Moving Expenses, 1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Mudd Facility - Photos, undated (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Mudd - Problem File, 1985 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry - Roofing, 1983-1987 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry - Shop Drawing Schedules, 1983 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry - Sprinkler System, 1983 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Steam System, 1983-1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] S.G. Mudd Building - Steel Testing, 1983 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Telephones, 1983-1985 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry Building - Job Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Mudd Chemistry Building - Change Orders, 1982-1983 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Payments to Contractor, 1983-1985 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Change Proposals, 1983 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry Building - Payment to Architects, 1986 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry Building - Payments to Engineer, 1981 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry - Sub-contracts, 1983 (Box 63)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Chemistry - Building Contracts, 1982 (Box 63)
  - Asbestos - M.H., 1987 (Box 63)
  - [Chicago Hall] Chicago Basement, 1987-1988 (Box 63)
  - ECM VIII [Energy Conservation Measure] Grant Reports, 1986-1987; (2 folders) (Box 64)
  - ECM VIII [Energy Conservation Measure] - Bids, 1986 (Box 64)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Chemistry Building - Brand / Biscraft Asbestos Abatement Bid, 1987 (Box 64)
  - Quadrangle Landscaping Re-design - Master Plans, Minutes, Project Expenditures and Correspondence, 1986-1990; (10 folders) (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker Field House [Correspondence and furnishings], 1983-1986 (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] Certificates of Completion, 1982 (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility Gym Floor, 1982, 1988; (2 folders) (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker Field House [General Correspondence], 1982 (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] H.W.R. System-Zoning, 1985 (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] Walker Field House Swimming Pool, 1981-1986 (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility - Payments to Contractor, 1981-1982 (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility - Electrical Shop Drawings, 1981-1983 (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] Proposed Physical Education Facilities [Correspondence and proposals], 1976-1979 (Box 64)
  - [Walker Field House] Athletic Facility - Punch List, 1982-1983 (Box 64)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] [Mudd Chemistry Building - Floor Plans and Meeting Minutes], 1982-1984 (Box 64)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Mudd Chemistry Building - Contract Documents [Outside Air Plenum, Railings and Doors], 1982 (Box 65)
  - [Mudd Chemistry] Seeley G Mudd Chemistry Building - Plant Operations, 1982 (Box 65)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Proposed D.C. to A.C. Conversion, Burns and Roe Inc. Sketches and Plans, 1955; (2 folders) (Box 65)
  - Evaluation of Asbestos Control Requirements, Vassar College, 1986 (Box 65)
  - Vassar College Asbestos Survey and Assessment Report, 1986 (Box 65)
  - Project Manual - Asbestos Abatement, 1986 (Box 65)
  - [Main Building] Project Manual - Energy Conservation Modifications - Vassar College, 1986; (2 folders) (Box 65)
  - [Main Building] Updated Detailed Energy Analysis, Main Building [Superceded], 1984 (Box 65)
  - [Main Building] Project Manual - Energy Conservation Modifications at the Main Building [Final Review Set], 1985; (3 folders) (Box 65)
  - [Main Building] Energy Conservation Modifications - [Plans and Sketches], undated (Box 65)
  - [Powerhouse Theater] Specifications for the Construction of Experimental Theatre, Vassar College, [1967?] (Box 65)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Vassar College Computer Center [Mechanical], 1966 (Box 65)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Vassar College Computer Center - [Johnson Control Condensed Catalogue and plans], 1966 (Box 65)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Biological Sciences Building - General Document 1, 1971 (Box 65)
  - Poughkeepsie Boots and Saddle Club [Executed License Agreement, Public Liability Insurance Certificate and associated correspondence], 1959-1964 (Box 65)
  - [Student Housing] Special Committee on Dining Facilities, 1964 Oct 1 (Box 65)
  - [College Center] College Center- Addendum Number 1 to the Specifications and Drawings [Office Copy], 1973 (Box 65)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Plant Operations and Addenda 1-5, 1971 (Box 65)
  - [Utilities - Electric] Specifications- Additions to the Electric Distribution System and other utilities for Vassar College, 1971 (Box 65)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Classroom Building- General Construction Work Specifications, 1987; (2 folders) (Box 65)
  - [Sanders Classroom] Sanders Classroom Building- Mechanical and Electrical Specifications, 1987 (Box 65)
  - [Olmsted Hall] Specifications - Biological Sciences Building, Divisions 6-16, undated (Box 66)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Computer Center - Drawings, 1966 (Box 66)
  - [Chicago Hall] Language Center Specifications, 1957; (2 copies) (Box 66)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] Contract Documents and Specifications to an All College Dining Hall for Vassar College [2 copies], 1971 (Box 66)
  - [Old Laundry Building] Vassar Computer Center Fire Protection Equipment Manual, 1966 (Box 66)
  - Elevator Specifications and Drawings, 1925; (2 folders) (Box 66)
  - Proposed Changes to the Mechanical Plant at Vassar College, 1916 (Box 66)
  - [Faculty Housing] Professor Abbey Leach House - Specifications, photocopy, circa 1910 (Box 66)
  - [Powerhouse Theater] Specifications for the Drama Workshop, Vassar College, 1972; (copy 1) (Box 66)
  - [Student Housing] Vassar College Residences-Specifications Addendum Two, 1971 (Box 67)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] All College Dining Hall - Daily Records, July 1, 1971-1973; (2 folders) (Box 67)
  - [Gordon Commons, ACDC] All College Dining Hall Plumbing Details, 1971-1974; (2 folders) (Box 67)